fox411.net 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Fox News

## INTRODUCTION

Fox News Network, LLC ("Fox News" or "we") wants you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information from and about you. This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with information collected through services such as websites, mobile sites, applications ("apps"), and widgets (collectively, the "Fox News Services"). By using Fox News Services, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

As set forth in our [Terms of Use](http://www.foxnews.com/about/terms-of-use/), the Fox News Services are for a general audience, are not targeted to children, and do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age.

This Privacy Policy applies to all users, including both those who use the Fox News Services without being registered with or subscribing to a Fox News Service and those who have registered with or subscribed to a Fox News Service. This Privacy Policy applies to Fox News's collection and use of your personal information (i.e., information that identifies a specific person, such as full name or email address). It also describes generally Fox News's practices for handling non-personal information (for example, interests, demographics and services usage).

## COLLECTION OF INFORMATION 

Fox News and our service providers collect the following information from and about you:

**Registration Information** is the information you submit to register for a Fox News Service, for example, to create an account, post comments, receive a newsletter, or enter a contest or sweepstakes. Registration Information may include, for example, name, email address, gender, zip code and birthday.

**Public Information and Posts** consist of comments or content that you post to the Fox News Services and the information about you that accompanies those posts or content, which may include a name, user name, comments, likes, status, profile information and picture. Public Information and Posts are always public, which means they are available to everyone and may be displayed in search results on external search engines.

**Information from Social Media.**. If you access or log-in to a Fox News Service through a social media service or connect a Fox News Service to a social media service, the information we collect may also include your user ID and/or user name associated with that social media service, any information or content you have permitted the social media service to share with us, such as your profile picture, email address or friends lists, and any information you have made public in connection with that social media service. When you access the Fox News Services through social media services or when you connect a Fox News Service to social media services, you are authorizing Fox News to collect, store, and use such information and content in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Activity Information.**.When you access and interact with the Fox News Services, we may collect certain information about those visits. For example, in order to permit your connection to the Fox News Services, our servers receive and record information about your computer, device, and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. If you access the Fox News Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device, geolocation data, or other transactional information for that device. At this time we do not respond to browser 'Do Not Track' signals, as we await the work of interested stakeholders and others to develop standards for how such signals should be interpreted.

Cookies and other tracking technologies (such as browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe Flash technology including cookies) are comprised of small bits of data that often include a de-identified or anonymous unique identifier. Websites, apps and other services send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer so the website can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that service. These technologies may also be used to collect and store information about your usage of the Fox News Services, such as pages you have visited, content you have viewed, search queries you have run and advertisements you have seen. If Fox News wishes to combine your personal information with information we obtain through these technologies in order to determine what messages Fox News provides to you, we will obtain your express affirmative consent.

Third parties that support the Fox News Services by serving advertisements or providing services, such as allowing you to share content or tracking aggregate Fox News Services usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect similar information. Fox News does not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies. For more information about third-party advertising networks and similar entities that use these technologies, including your choices with respect to them, see the section entitled "To deliver relevant advertisements," below

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information. Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe's website, see <http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security/privacy_policy/faq.html>. Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features, content or personalization available through the Fox News Services.

Information from Other Sources. We may supplement the information we collect with information from other sources, such as publicly available information from social media services, commercially available sources and information from our Fox News Affiliates or business partners.

## USE AND DISCLOSURE

We use the information we collect from and about you to provide the Fox News Services and features to you, including: to measure and improve those Fox News Services and features; to improve your experience with both online and off-line Fox News Services by delivering content you will find relevant and interesting, including advertising and marketing messages; to allow you to comment on content and to provide you with customer support and to respond to inquiries. When the information collected from or about you does not identify you as a specific person, we may use that information for any purpose or share it with third parties. 

We use the information we collect from and about you for these additional purposes:

**To allow service providers to assist us in providing and managing the Fox News Services.** Fox News may make your information available to certain third party service providers, such as contractors, agents or sponsors, who help us manage or provide the Fox News Services.

**To allow social sharing functionality.** If you log in with or connect a social media service account with Fox News Services, we may share your user name, picture, and likes, as well as your activities and comments with other Fox News Services users and with your friends associated with your social media service. We may also share the same information with the social media service provider. By logging in with or connecting your Fox News Services account with a social media service, you are authorizing us to share information we collect from and about you with the social media service provider, other users and your friends and you understand that the social media service's use of the shared information will be governed by the social media service's privacy policy. If you do not want your personal information shared in this way, please do not connect your social media service account with your Fox News Services account and do not participate in social sharing on Fox News Services.

**To deliver relevant advertisements.** Fox News and our service providers may use the information we collect from and about you to deliver relevant ads to you when you use the Fox News Services or another service. As noted above, third-party advertising networks and advertisers may use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track information such as demographic information, inferred interests, aggregated information, and activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests. To find out more about third-party advertising networks and similar entities that use these technologies, see [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/), and to opt-out of such advertising networks' and services' advertising practices, go to <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>. If you would like to opt-out of such ad networks' and services' advertising practices, go to <http://www.aboutads.info/choices> to opt-out in desktop and mobile web browsers. You may download the AppChoices app at <http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices> to opt-out in mobile apps. To opt out of this type of advertising from Outbrain Inc, visit Outbrain's website at <http://www.outbrain.com/privacy>.

**To contact you.** Fox News may periodically send promotional materials or notifications related to the Fox News Services. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials, you can follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. There are certain service notification emails that you may not opt-out of, such as notifications of changes to the Fox News Services or policies. If you have installed a mobile app and you wish to stop receiving push notifications, you can change the settings either on your mobile device or through the app.

**To share with our Fox News Affiliates.** Fox News may share your information with Fox News Affiliates for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. Users who visit Affiliated Companies' services should still refer to their separate privacy policies, which may differ in some respects from this Privacy Policy.

**To share with business partners.** Fox News may share your information with business partners to permit them to send you marketing communications consistent with your choices.

**To protect the rights of Fox News and others.** There may be instances when Fox News may disclose your information, including situations where Fox News has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of Fox News, our Fox News Affiliates or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements and our terms of use); (ii) protect the safety, privacy, and security of users of the Fox News Services or members of the public; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; (iv) comply with the law or legal process; or (v) respond to requests from public and government authorities.

**To complete a merger or sale of assets.** If Fox News sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, Fox News may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

## SECURITY

Fox News uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification.

## USER ACCESS AND CONTROL

If you would like to access, review, correct, update, suppress, or otherwise limit our use of your personal information you have previously provided directly to us, you may contact us as outlined in Section 7. In your request, please include your email address, name, address, and telephone number and specify clearly what information you would like to access, change, update, or suppress. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable.

We give you many choices regarding our use and disclosure of your personal information for marketing purposes. You may opt-out from:

**Receiving electronic communications from us:** If you no longer want to receive marketing-related emails from us on a going-forward basis, you may opt-out of receiving these marketing-related emails by following the unsubscribe instructions in the email.

**Cancelling your account.** To cancel your account, email [mailto:deleteaccount@foxnews.com](mailto:deleteaccount@foxnews.com), subject, "Delete My Account" and include the email address that you registered your account with (if different from the email address you're sending the email from). Remember that even after you cancel your account, copies of some information from your account may remain viewable in some circumstances - where, for example, you have shared information with a third-party application or web site. We may also retain backup information related to your account on our servers for some time after cancelation for fraud detection or to comply with applicable law or our internal security policies. Because of the nature of caching technology, your account may not be instantly inaccessible to others, and there may be a delay in the removal of the content from elsewhere on the Internet and from search engines.

## OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION

**Updates to Privacy Policy.** Fox News may modify this Privacy Policy. Please look at the Effective Date at the top of this Privacy Policy to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Fox News Services. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy that expand our rights to use the personal information we have already collected from you, we will notify you and provide you with a choice about our future use of that information.

**Location of Data.** The Fox News Services are hosted in and managed from the United States. If you are a user located outside the United States, you understand and consent to having any personal information processed in the United States. United States data protection and other relevant laws may not be the same as those in your jurisdiction. This includes the use of cookies and other tracking technologies as described above. As a result, please read this Privacy Policy with care.

**Linked Services.** The Fox News Services may also be linked to sites operated by unaffiliated companies, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, games, newsletters, contests or sweepstakes, or applications developed and maintained by unaffiliated companies. Fox News is not responsible for the privacy practices of unaffiliated companies, and once you leave the Fox News Services or click an advertisement you should check the applicable privacy policy of the other service.

**Data Retention.** We will retain your information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or allowed by law.

Remember that even after you cancel your account, copies of some information from your account may remain viewable in some circumstances where, for example, you have shared information with social media or other services. Because of the nature of caching technology, your account may not be instantly inaccessible to others. We may also retain backup information related to your account on our servers for some time after cancelation for fraud detection or to comply with applicable law or our internal security policies. It is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information due to technical constraints, contractual, financial or legal requirements.

**Sensitive Information.** We ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive personal information (such as social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the Fox News Services or otherwise.

## CONTACT US

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Email: [ldepartment@foxnews.com](mailto:ldepartment@foxnews.com)

Mail:

Fox News Network, LLC  
1211 Avenue of the Americas, 15th Floor  
New York, NY 10036  
Attention: Legal Department
